Inglês 

-almost = quase (OK)
-assorted = sortido (OK)
-briefing = ?
-childhood = infância (OK)
-covered = coberto (OK)
-deployed = implantado (OK)
-ensures = garante (OK)
-evening = noite (OK)
-foot = pé (OK)
-gray = cinza (OK)
-Hi = Oi (OK)
-offer = oferta (OK)
-often = frequentemente (OK)
-proud = orgulhoso (OK)
-ranks =  classificações (OK)
-relies = confia  (OK)
-richly = ricamente (OK)
-shoddy = malfeito  (OK)
-sideways = lateralmente  (OK)
-sneak = esgueirar  (OK)
-struggled = lutado  (OK)
-thirteenth = décimo terceiro  (OK)
-throw-away = jogar fora  (OK)
-Treasured = valorizo (OK)

Expressões :

Bail out = 
Beaver away = 
Bottom out = 

Chicken out = 
Cut back = 

Dress up = Vestir com as melhores roupas
Drop in = Visitar sem avisar
Duck out = Sair rápido sem anunciar

Fall through = 
Ferret out = 
Fill out = Completar
Fish for = 
Fish out = 

Go under = 
Hang out =
Have on = 
Horse around = 

Join in = Participar
Kick off = 

Lay off =  
Let down = 
Let out = 
Level off = 

Monkey around = 

Pull out = 
Put back = Delay or postpone

Rabbit on = 
Rat on = 
Run out of = 

Slip on = 
Sort out = Organizar ou consertar conteúdos de algo

Take in = 
Take on = 
Take over = Comerça a ter controle / responsabilidade de algo
Thrown on = 
Turn up = 

Wolf down = Comer muito rápido
Worm out of =
Wrap up = 

Zip up = 

Português > Inglês 

Ar condicionado = 
Fogão = 
Geladeira = 
Secador de roupa = 
Ventilador = 

almost
I almost want to give a history lession or pass links to various wikis or country websites

assorted
And here's a text document that contains all the various assorted info of the game such as officer stats, hidden game mechanics, etc

briefing
Naval units are the topic of this briefing

covered
This is covered in more detail in the section on Advanced Tactics

deployed
You have 50 units deployed.

ensures
And promoting one later in the game can be the factor that ensures victory

evening
The evening is spoiled.Fine!

foot
As an infantry specialist, her foot soldier do more damage and capture faster.

gray
Clan of the gray wolf

proud
We are proud to introduce you to another dimension from Koei world of quality games.

ranks
The horizontal lines on a chessboard are called ranks

relies
High firepower, but he relies solely on strength.

shoddy
His shoddy technique sometimes reduces the damage his units deal

sideways
Theys can only move forwards: never sideways or backwards

sneak
En Passant allows players to capture pawns that opponents may be trying to sneak past their own pawns

struggled
You struggled against the weather, but did well, DAN. You won!

throw-away
Never underestime your pawns or view them as throw-away pieces...

thirteenth
The thirteenth century was marked by turmoil in Europe, Asia and northern Africa.


quase
Eu quase quero dar uma aula de história ou passar links para vários wikis ou sites de países

sortido
E aqui está um documento de texto que contém todas as várias informações variadas do jogo, como estatísticas de oficiais, mecânicas de jogo ocultas, etc.

briefing
Unidades navais são o tópico deste briefing

implantado
Você tem 50 unidades implantadas.

pé
Como especialista em infantaria, seu soldado de infantaria causa mais dano e captura mais rápido.

cinza
Clã do lobo cinzento

orgulhoso
Estamos orgulhosos de apresentar a você outra dimensão do mundo de jogos de qualidade da Koei.

relies
Alto poder de fogo, mas ele depende somente da força.

shoddy
Sua técnica de má qualidade às vezes reduz o dano que suas unidades causam

struggled
Você lutou contra o clima, mas se saiu bem, DAN. Você venceu!

third-century
O século XIII foi marcado por turbulências na Europa, Ásia e norte da África.